tawk.link 2018-06-23

# Privacy Policy | tawk.to

Your privacy is important to us at tawk.to. Here is how your Privacy is maintained :

  * We don’t request access to you personal information unless we truly need it to provide the service eg: Your gender or income levels are irrelevant to us, so we don’t ask you for that information.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which adhere to those principles :

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please initiate a chat with us, or [send us an email](mailto:support@tawk.to) at any time.

Tawk.to operates an web application and corresponding mobile apps (on https://www.tawk.to). It is tawk.to’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our services.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most internet-service operators, tawk.to collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers, apps and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, geographical location, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. tawk.to’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how tawk.to’s visitors use its services, and to provide tawk.to users the ability to understand how their visitors use their services. From time to time, tawk.to may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its services.

tawk.to also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users that use the services and visitors.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to tawk.to’s websites and users of tawk.to’s apps choose to interact with tawk.to in ways that require tawk.to to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that tawk.to gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask users of our app to provide an email address. In each case, tawk.to collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with tawk.to. tawk.to does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Additionally, if: (a) you are established in the European Economic Area (EEA); (b) you provide goods or services to customers in the EEA; or (c) you are otherwise subject to the requirements of the EU General Data Protection Regulation, tawk.to’s collection and use of personal information of any European residents is also subject to our [Data Processing Addendum](https://www.tawk.to/data-protection/dpa-data-processing-addendum/).

**Aggregated Statistics**  
tawk.to may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, tawk.to does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
tawk.to discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that:

  * (i) need to know that information in order to process it on tawk.to’s behalf or to provide services available at tawk.to’s webservices, and
  * (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using tawk.to’s webservices, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. tawk.to will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, tawk.to discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when tawk.to believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of tawk.to, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of tawk.to and have supplied your email address, tawk.to may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with tawk.to and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. tawk.to takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. tawk.to uses cookies to help tawk.to identify and track visitors, their usage of tawk.to website, and their website access preferences. tawk.to visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using tawk.to’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of tawk.to’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**  
If tawk.to, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that tawk.to goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of tawk.to may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by tawk.to and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, tawk.to may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in tawk.to’s sole discretion. tawk.to encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of these services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contacting us**  
If you have questions about this policy, you can contact us at [support@tawk.to](mailto:support@tawk.to).

Creative Commons: This privacy policy is based on one developed by Automattic (http://automattic.com/privacy/) and is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 2.5 License. Emoji art supplied by [EmojiOne](http://emojione.com/)
